# MANUELE FRAU

UI/UX DESIGNER

CASE STUDIES AVAILABLE ON behance.net/manuelefrau

ITALIA +39 333 3878202 SUOMI +358 417248370

manuelefraucontact@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/manuele-frau

## **PROFILE**

I am a UI/UX designer with coding skills, with strong customer service experience gained in the hospitality and food industries.

I am also a musician, sound artist and audio engineer with a deep artistic mindset.

I like to help others and solve problems and I feel satisfied when I achieve goals. I would love to work for a company or agency where I can grow while expressing my creativity.

## SKILLS

## My key skills are:

- Visual design
- Interaction design
- Branding
- Typography & Iconography
- Style guides
- Mobile app design
- · User research and testing
- User personas
- User flows
- Wireframing & prototyping

## Proficient with design tools such as:

- Sketch
- Adobe XD
- InVision
- Affinity Photo
- Photoshop
- Flinto
- Blender
- Atom/Visual Studio Code

## WORK EXPERIENCE

Resturant Shift Supervisor Fafa's Plats Oy • Helsinki, Finland	2019 - 2021
Front Desk Agent Dharma Hotel & Luxury Suites • Rome, Italy	2015 - 2019
Freelance Audio Technician Radiospeaker • Rome, Italy	2013 - 2015
Freelance Production Assistant Kick Agency • Rome, Italy	2011 - 2013

## EDUCATION

Ul Design Bootcamp Career Foundry • Online Course	2021 - 2022
Frontend Development for Designers Career Foundry • Online Course	2021 - 2022
Front Desk Agent Course CTS Tourism School • Rome, Italy	2015
Sound Engineering Course Adriatico Institute • Rome, Italy	2013
Fine Art Diploma ISA RM2 Art Institute • Rome, Italy	2000 - 2005

## LANGUAGES

English	Italian	Spanish	Finnish
Fluent	Native	Basic	Basic

<sup>\*</sup> If you use different tools that works well in your workflow, I would be happy to learn it.